♪The night wind shakes off
the withered leaves♪
♪I open the window and gaze at the moon♪
♪Haze spreads across the river,
lanterns drifting♪
♪I hear the memories rustling♪
♪Garden flowers shed petals one by one♪
♪Candlelight flickers,
swaying with melancholy♪
♪I sigh by the lamp over the long night♪
♪Past memories unfold scene by scene♪
♪It's all your face♪
♪Boldly trampling over my heart♪
♪Two measures of ink I take,
one for love miswritten♪
♪And another for youth passed♪
♪With endless sorrow,
I once traced your silhouette♪
♪Two measures of ink I take,
one for joy and sorrow♪
♪And another for parting and reunion♪
♪I write until splendor fades,
and I am no more♪
=Prelude of the White Snake=
=Episode 17=
M-Miss Bai,
I haven't finished bathing yet.
Could you please leave?
Miss Bai,
don't come any closer.
I don't have anything on.
Are you scared?
O-Of course not.
It's not like I'm naked.
You need not be so nervous.
Miss Bai, this is truly improper.
Please step out.
But I won't do anything to you.
I just want to wash your back for you.
Young Master Xu,
what is this?
You can't escape my grasp.
After ten years,
you've finally shown up.
I will hunt you down.
Who is it?
The enemy
who killed my parents.
Young Master Xu,
what is this?
It's good.
Stop struggling.
You can't get out.
Being absorbed by me
is only a matter of time.
You should have seen it.
The dowry Aunt gave me was so beautiful.
Why is everyone so nice to you?
No,
now they are nice to me.
Miss Bai, are you inside?
I'm here.
Miss Bai, there's something
I want to ask you.
Are you here to talk about our wedding?
N-No.
We can talk about that later.
I wanted to ask you,
do you really not remember this?
Of course I do.
But it doesn't matter.
You are what matters.
No. She isn't me.
Miss Bai, I need to go.
See?
He can't tell us apart at all.
I'll win him over sooner or later.
It's just a matter of time.
Here.
My embroidered ball!
Amazing!
This little thing is quite fun.
What is this?
The embroidered ball
my younger sister gave me.
An embroidered ball?
Good, it's mine now.
Give me back my ball!
- Give me back my ball!
All right, no more fuss.
Here, take this.
It could buy you several balls.
Suzhen, Suzhen.
Suzhen.
Suzhen,
guess what fun new thing I brought you.
What is it?
Take a guess.
I really can't guess.
An embroidered ball.
In the mortal realm, this is given
to children as a blessing,
a plaything for their spare time.
I'm giving it to you now.
Shall we play together?
Alright, I'll take it.
Suzhen, let's play together for a bit.
Qing, I have things to do right now.
I'll play with you
when I have time, alright?
Suzhen.
Be good, Qing.
Suzhen, just play with me
for a little while, please?
Qing.
Could you stop bothering me?
Fine.
Do you really not remember this?
Of course I do.
But it doesn't matter.
Are you scared?
I just want to wash your back for you.
(Is she really my Suzhen?)
It's Xu Xian again.
All she thinks about now is Xu Xian.
There's no room left for me.
But she did say I was the only one.
Why did she learn
those bad habits from humans?
I just can't accept it.
She chose love
over friendship. I get it.
You don't get it.
I'm supposed to be the most important.
I just wanted to play
with her a bit longer.
What did I do wrong?
You did nothing wrong.
It's all his fault.
Seriously. You know what?
If I knew how to shapeshift,
I'd turn him into a dog, alright?
Or turn him into a wooden post
and make him...
- That's your idea?
- Stand right here.
Scold him all you want.
I'll let you be the older sister.
Nonsense.
You don't get it.
You have no idea.
You're annoying.
You're upset if I don't talk
and even more upset if I talk too much.
Unbelievable.
Miss Bai,
Miss Qing
hasn't been in the best mood lately.
I think you should
find time to talk to her
and cheer her up.
You came all this way
just to blame me for neglecting Qing?
I'm not blaming you.
The sisterly bond between you two
is beyond me anyway.
I know Miss Qing respects and loves you.
You're her only family, truly.
You mean a lot to her.
She means a lot to me too.
Exactly, which is why
you should care for her more.
After over five centuries of cultivation
and finally a chance
to achieve immortality,
do you think it matters to me or not?
Qing does matter, of course,
but there are priorities.
Little Master Fahai,
you understand this, don't you?
I do. I do.
♪I also gave my youth to someone♪
♪I must admit, you made the journey♪
♪When loving you
became instinct, what's left♪
♪Seals a fate too brutal to amend♪
♪Clumsy and new, we gave our first kiss♪
♪Never thought passionate eyes
would turn cold♪
♪I thought of pulling away,
but I'd barely begun♪
♪Having loved you so deep,
how could I love another♪
♪Even if we're strangers again,
why deny we loved♪
♪Though I'm stubborn,
I never stopped you from loving others♪
♪I shouldn't have been so foolish
to think there was still hope♪
♪But you won't even admit what we had♪
♪Even if we're strangers again,
why deny we loved♪
♪Though I have questions,
I never questioned you♪
♪I'll lock you away and set myself free♪
♪After all, I'm the one you deny♪
♪Having ever loved♪